Everyone, the midterm exams
will be held in two weeks.
Stella Stars will be awarded to
the top two students with highest scores
in each of the four subjects.
On the other hand, anyone who fails
the exams will receive Tonitrus Bolts.
So please give it your very best.
Now I will return the history quiz
that you all took the other day.
Alice Paulet.
Anya, are you also worried about the test?
I'm not worried.
Anya has been studying a lot recently.
Anya Forger.
Not elegant. You must take
extra lessons after school.
Damian, you're so good at imitating her.
You've really captured her dumb look.
I hate the second son,
but I learned something today.
I can ace the history test,
as long as I read the second son's mind.
Hey Forger. Why are you laughing?
As punishment,
you're getting another worksheet.
I'm getting home late because
my teacher was being a bully.
The moon is already getting brighter
and saying hello.
Oh!
Father!
-Welcome!
-What is it? What's the commotion?
Father, how big will the moon be
in two weeks?
The moon?
In two weeks, it'll be the new moon.
Are you planning on stargazing?
I knew it!
By the way, you have a test in two weeks.
All right! Let's do some studying
before we have dinner.
I'll help you with anything.
Hey. Let's study.
Anya is the super telepath
who saved the world.
But even Anya has a weakness.
The researchers were calling the weakness
an "Eclipse" or something like that.
Every month, on the day when
the moon disappears,
Anya loses her power as a telepath.
The exam falls on the day of the eclipse!
Which means that Anya…
won't be able to cheat!
What should I do?
I'm facing the biggest crisis of my life!
Oh right! Bond, look into the future
and show me what's on the test!
Hamburger steak!
Tonight's dinner
is Hamburger steak that Father made!
Hooray!
How did you know?
Did you look inside the refrigerator?
Shall we eat?
Yum.
What should I do about the exam?
I totally fell asleep!
That's why I said that we should study
last night.
We have today off, so I'll help you study.
The midterm exams will cover
four subjects.
Which means there's a possibility
that she may get four Tonitrus Bolts.
I've already given up on
the possibility of four Stella Stars.
Together with the final exams,
she just might get eight
Tonitrus Bolts during this school year.
I must prevent her from getting expelled
until I can go to the reception
to see Desmond.
I must strengthen her
basic academic skills…
while proceeding with the reception…
There's so much going on in Father's mind
that I can't concentrate on studying.
I have no idea what
she doesn't understand.
Oh, that's right!
The other day, I asked Yuri if he can
be Anya's tutor,
and he said that he'd be happy to help.
Should I call him?
Will that be all right?
Uncle.
Yahoo! I'm here, Sis!
That was fast.
Welcome, Yuri.
Long time no see, Yuri.
I guess we'll need to be
prepared for sudden visits.
What? Why is Loid Forger here?
You should work on the weekends!
Anya, this is Yuri, my younger brother.
This is that damn Forger's daughter?
I'm Anya. I'm Father's daughter.
Nice to meet you.
He's the scary Secret Police.
Sis is like a goddess! Hey Sis! Sis!
Hey, you should greet her too.
Anya's getting a heartburn.
Are you all right?
Should we study after you take
a little break?
How are things lately?
The Foreign Ministry must have been
busy with the summit a few days ago.
I'll gather some information.
Oh… well, yeah…
I'm sure the State Security already knows
that Twilight disguised as the Minister.
It was an emergency but it was risky.
Is this jerk mocking me because
the summit was delayed by the terrorists?
I won't let you bring me down in front
of my sister, you sneaky bastard!
-I must be on guard.
-I need to look cool.
Spy versus the Secret Police.
How exciting!
Uncle doesn't know about
Father's true identity. So Father wins!
What is it? If you're feeling better,
start studying.
I don't want to be in the way,
so I'll go do some shopping.
Okay.
Now I have time to
complete my other mission.
But what about the battle…
All right, shall we get started?
Sis asked me for a favor,
so I said yes without much thought,
but why do I have to help out
this dumb looking kid?
Try solving this problem.
It's so unfair that she gets to spend
every day with Sis.
I'll give her a hard question
to show her the harsh reality.
What? You answered everything correctly?
Wow, how amazing!
It seems like you don't need to study.
Oh no.
I have to study because I can't cheat
on the day of the exam.
That was just a coincidence.
I guessed all of those answers.
What? Yeah, I thought so.
You couldn't have answered these.
No. That's wrong!
You're so slow-witted!
Put more effort into it!
I am!
Yuri, please teach her more nicely.
I don't want Anya to get expelled.
Anya wants to go to school.
That is also the wish of my late wife.
Please, Yuri. I'm really counting on you.
Okay?
S… S… Sis!
But I don't know if she has the potential…
Anya will work hard!
I want to become an Imperial Scholar,
and make it big
so that I can buy lots of
delicious food for Mother!
-What a good kid!
-Oh my!
She's an angel!
What the heck is Imperial Scholar?
Anya, I'll prepare some tea and snacks.
Yay!
She thinks so highly of Sis…
No, let's calm down.
She's the daughter of the man
who stole Sis. Don't be deceived!
But, if I help her
to ace the exam, that will make Sis happy
and she'll say, "I love you, Yuri!"
All right. I'll do it! I'll teach her!
Hey, you made another error.
It's okay, don't worry.
What's important, is for you to realize
why you made that error.
For this part, don't think too hard
and focus on the verb.
Okay.
This is so nostalgic.
Sis, this is how you solve this problem.
It's easy, right?
Really?
Hey, you can do it.
You don't like studying?
I hate it. Do you like it, Uncle?
Are you a weirdo?
Don't call me Uncle. I…
When I was young, I was frustrated
by my own helplessness.
I wanted to be of use to Sis.
That's why I studied really hard.
Every time I solved one problem,
I felt like I had
grown one centimeter taller.
I was so happy.
I worked really hard on language arts.
Because I figured that
if I became eloquent,
I could become a journalist or a lawyer
and make Sis's world a better place.
I worked hard on chemistry and biology.
Because if I study anatomy and medicine,
I'd be able to cure my sister
when she got sick.
I worked hard on mathematics and physics.
Because I thought it would provide Sis
with a safe and comfortable life.
In the end, I chose to become a diplomat,
but I'm using everything I've learned.
Wow.
Someone important in the past said,
"Knowledge is power."
If you want to become a responsible adult,
train, and work out your brain!
Chihuahua power?
No!
-If I study, I can make medicine?
-That's right!
-Can I make rockets?
-Of course!
-Can I conquer the world?
-Well, as for that…
Oh… um… wait, you want to conquer?
All right! Here's the next exercise.
Forget about the exam in front of you!
Look ahead to your successful future!
Look ahead to that future
where Sis is smiling brightly!
Please don't teach her anything weird.
Well? Were you able to master
this form of grammar?
What's grammar?
This was seriously a waste of time!
I'm leaving. I've had enough.
Yuri!
That's right. I have to study too.
I still have a lot to learn.
If I was more competent,
I would've been able to capture Twilight.
I could've eliminated
the threat against the West.
I need to become stronger
in order to protect Sis and my country.
Sorry Sis. I have to go.
He's as impatient as ever.
He didn't even try my homemade dessert.
It's delicious.
Oh no, he ate all of it.
I'll make some more.
No, it's okay. Anya is full right now.
Back then, if I had been able to
read the clock,
or if I knew how to defuse the bomb,
then I might have been able to
help Father succeed his mission.
I'll go study in my room.
Okay. I'm so proud of you.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Loid.
Anya is studying really hard.
Is that right? I'm glad.
Let's see.
Foreign language?
Yes! She was working so hard on that.
FOREIGN LANGUAGE
Foreign language is not part of
the midterm exams.
TWO WEEKS LATER
Operation Strix…
might fail…
Anya, it's finally the exams.
How do you think you'll do?
Becky, you'd be shocked if you knew about
my chihuahua power right now.
Huh? What kind of power is that?
Well, it sounds like you're confident.
I'll have to do my best too!
Now we will begin
the midterm exams of the first semester!
I think I failed the math exam.
I might have gotten 80 points
on language arts.
MISSION 18: DAYBREAK
How were the tests by
the first graders this year?
I only took a quick glance,
but it didn't look too good.
Maybe the problems were a little too hard.
That's how it should be.
I'm sure we'll have those
parents again this year who bribe us
to give their kids good grades.
But our principal right now
will not allow such injustice.
Whoever takes the lead in this school,
will eventually take the lead
in this country.
Tampering with the tests
will not be tolerated.
These exam papers will determine
the future of our country.
We must store them in a secure place
until the tests are graded.
My name is Twilight.
I'm carrying out Operation Strix
in order to secure peace.
But there are dark clouds looming
over that operation right now.
Exams with chances of the Tonitrus Bolts.
Anya's test results will probably be…
No, she will definitely…
Anya feels like she can do it!
She'll definitely fail.
In that case, I'll have to maneuver things
behind the scenes.
But I know from experience that it's risky
to just memorize the correct answers.
Therefore this time,
I will be more precise and direct.
I will tamper with the tests
before they are graded.
-Goodbye, Teacher.
-Okay.
The issue lies with
this school's security.
It's not as tricky as the security
for the entrance exam,
but the vault is strictly guarded
and it will take time to gain entry.
I can't be careless and cause
the school to become suspicious.
I must accomplish this
without leaving a single trace.
Who is that? He's not a teacher here.
That's an unfamiliar face.
In fact,
he is obviously suspicious.
My name is Daybreak.
I'm an elite spy hired by a company.
My mission is to tamper with
a particular student's test paper.
This is such an easy job. What?
You want to know the origin of my name?
Apparently, there's an amazing spy
named Twilight working in this country.
So I personally gave myself this name,
as the rising star
who is capable of challenging him.
Twilight of the West,
and Daybreak of the East.
Let's see who the ultimate spy is!
This is my first mission.
Watch and see
the beginning of a new legend.
He's heading towards the North Wing?
Is he here for the same purpose?
What's with those unnecessary moves?
It's hard to believe,
but is he also a spy?
This is not good. If he creates trouble,
it would put me at a disadvantage too.
You idiot! That route is dangerous…
They're guards making their rounds.
Oh crap.
Stop it, you've got no chance.
It's annoying to hear that from you.
Just you wait and see.
I'll ask for her number tomorrow.
He was able to fool them?!
I have no idea how, but he did it!
Was it camouflage?
He's got amazing strength and nerve!
Did he use that technique because
he's aware of the human's blind spots?
Is he someone amazing?
It's locked!
What should I do?
If he's going to be a hindrance,
I can get rid of him
before he enters the building.
Or while he's distracted with
the door, I can…
Hey! Are you an idiot?!
What will you do if someone catches you?
Is he a robber instead of a spy?
No, he's lousy even for a robber.
Traces of breaking and entering will
raise suspicion of tampering!
I'll make it seem as if it was an accident
during soccer practice.
Sorry, soccer team!
North Wing.
Damn it. He's boldly walking in
without a care in the world!
I want to intervene, but I can't be
careless when I know nothing about him!
What's his purpose for coming here?
Can't he be quieter?
What?
Whoa, are you serious? No one told me
that there's a guard in here too!
There's no way
I can get in unless that guard
opens the door for me!
What should I do?
This is the only way inside.
Who are you?
What are you doing here at this hour?
I had some errands to run around here.
In the vaults? Excuse me,
but are you a member of the faculty?
Show me your ID.
Huh? ID?
Oh… it's me! Remember?
I teach information science.
It's me, the really famous…
If you don't have your ID, please leave.
Oh come on. Help me out this once.
-Please?
-You want me to call the police?
This isn't good.
It'll be a hassle if the police come.
Information science…
-Come on…
-Excuse me.
I found this on the ground over there,
isn't this yours?
I'm so glad I brought extra IDs
for various departments.
What?
I've never seen that…
Newly appointed teacher Mr. Brown,
you can enter with this ID.
Oh! That's right!
I guess I dropped that somewhere!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
He wrote down his mission
on the palm of his hand!
You've got to be kidding me!
Wait, is this some kind of a trap?
You may enter.
Thank you for your help.
I was able to read two student ID numbers
and the word "tamper."
I guess he was a spy after all.
And those student ID numbers belong to
the Desmond brothers.
Who is he working for?
No, I can't be too hasty.
I need information.
This is it, huh? Vault number seven.
I took a memo of the passcode too.
I'm so good at this.
Oh?
Did I write it down incorrectly?
I'm going to use the restroom first.
Please go ahead. Bye.
There is no restroom in this building.
I refuse to believe that
Operation Strix exists
because of people who hire
idiots like him!
What a hassle.
Thanks for your help, you fool!
Enjoy your nap for a little while.
I'll carry him inside so that
the guard won't see him.
Let's see.
Where are the first grader's tests?
I guess it'll be safer to do my job
after he leaves.
Even his blows are sloppy.
What? There's a lock on this case too?
Damn it! It doesn't open!
Hurry up!
All right! Mission complete!
How perfect!
I'm shocked by my own genius talent!
More than likely,
I've already surpassed Twilight.
Sorry, Twilight!
All right! Tonight I'm going to buy beef
instead of pork!
What did you say about me?
If you're done, just shut up and go home!
This will heighten my reputation
and I'll get so many jobs!
My name might even make it
in the newspaper!
No, maybe not the newspaper.
Since I'm a spy.
No one will ever notice me.
All right. In addition to modifying
the answers, I'll also add my signature!
If you're a spy,
don't willingly leave your trace behind!
-What?
-Oh.
You bastard. You were awake, huh?
Damn it. What's wrong with me?
I couldn't stay silent!
I'm sorry. I didn't see anything.
I promise not to tell anyone.
So please spare my life!
Should I just get rid of him?
Hey, do you take me for a fool?
You should tell everyone
about my successful work!
Huh?
Listen up. My name is Daybreak.
Tell everyone about what
a dependable and cool spy I was
in a casual, yet dramatic way!
You can even exaggerate.
For example, say that I slipped through
the wall or caught a bullet with my hand.
But don't give out details
about my mission.
Thanks a bunch, my brother!
All right, adios!
Who the hell was he anyway?
Are the Desmond brothers failing so badly
that they need help from that idiot?
No, it's the opposite.
It's been modified to make them fail.
The people who hired him are most likely
Desmon's rival company,
or a political opponent.
I can't have them get expelled.
I'll change it to their original answers.
I'll decipher their original answers
and trace their handwriting. Damn it.
I'm having to do extra work now.
All right. I'm done.
Both of those brothers are capable.
Especially that older brother
got almost 100% on all subjects.
Compared to that…
Let's see how Anya did.
Anya… Here it is.
This is…
FIVE DAYS LATER
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
The test results are displayed
in the courtyard! Let's go see them!
Damian's rank is…
There it is! You're in 11th place overall.
You got 94 points for history!
Second place in our grade!
You're getting a Stella Star!
You're amazing, Damian!
Congratulations.
Oh no. I'm in 46th place.
I guess that's not so bad. I don't see
your name, Anya. What's your ranking?
Start looking from the bottom.
To tell you the truth,
Anya already knew the results.
I heard Father saying in his mind
that he saw my tests.
There you are, Anya!
213th…
You've got nothing to worry about!
Let's work hard next time!
It seems like you didn't fail.
Good for you.
This is too sad. Let's go.
That's right!
Anya didn't get a single Tonitrus Bolt!
You did very well!
-Well done.
-Father's mission.
It's somewhat safe for now.
Wow. She's smiling despite her ranking?
You're so positive, Anya!
Just as I expected of you!
Father! Anya worked hard on her test!
How can you be so proud when you
almost failed all subjects?
This is not what I had imagined.
I have to be more strict in preparation
for the final exams.
How amazing, Anya. When you add
all the scores, it's over 100 points!
Well,
she unexpectedly passed all of the tests
on her own.
I guess she's doing the best she can.
Thanks to her, I'm able to continue
my mission. I should show my gratitude.
Oh.
Why are you smiling?
Are you reflecting on your mistakes?
-We'll review the tests after dinner.
-Oh no!
What? The mission failed?
That can't be. I made sure to…
What? I'm fired? Wait!
Oh no! But that was supposed to be
the beginning of a new legend!
MISSION 19: THE REVENGE PLOT AGAINST
DESMOND - THE MOTHER BECOMES THE WIND
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita